Register of the China Defense Supplies Records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Departments file, 1940-1944 (Box 13-25)
  - Motor Transport/Transportation Department
    - Gasoline containers, 1942-1943. (Folder 19: 5)
      See also Transportation fuel executive file and Departments file - Aviation Department
    - Index, 1941 (Folder 19: 6)
    - Parts for Friends' Ambulance Unit, 1943 (Folder 19: 7)
    - Railroad materials, 1941-1943. (Folder 19: 8)
      Includes correspondence on Yunnan-Burma Railway
    - Repair shops, 1942-1943 (Folder 19: 9)
    - Requirements. (Folder 19)
      See also Oversize materials.
      - Chinese requirements, 1941 (Folder 19: 10)
      - Chinese government requirements, Ministry of Communications, 1944 (Folder 19: 11)
      - Memoranda, undated (Folder 19: 12)
      - Requirements, assignments and shipments plus weight, 1943 (Folder 19: 13)
      - Sichang-Sadiya Highway, undated (Folder 19: 14)
      - Transportation requirements, Part 1 (explanatory statements), 1942-1943 (Folder 19: 15)
      - Transportation requirements, Part 2 (list of requirements), 1942 (Folder 19: 16)
      - Transportation requirements, Part 3 (list of requirements), 1942 (Folder 19: 17)
    - Research for history of China Defense Supplies report (summary of transportation supplies), 1942 (Folder 19: 18)
    - Retreading plant, tires and tubes, 1941-1943 (Folder 20: 1)
    - Shipments, conserving space, 1942 (Folder 20: 2)
    - Spare parts (Folder 20)
      - General, 1942-1944 (Folder 20: 3)
      - Bishop, McCormick & Bishop, 1943-1944 (Folder 20: 4)
      - L. K. Taylor, 1943 (Folder 20: 5)
    - Statistics about assignments, 1943 (Folder 20: 6)
    - Statistics and summaries, 1942-1943. (Folder 20: 7)
      See also Oversize materials
    - Status of allocations, 1941-1942 (Folder 20: 8)
    - Status of ordnance vehicle requirements, 1943 (Folder 20: 9)
    - Tractors for the Air Force, 1942 (Folder 20: 10)
    - Trucks, 1941-1943 (Folder 20: 11)
    - Trucks inside China, 1942-1944 (Folder 20: 12)
    - Miscellany, 1942-1944 (Folder 20: 13)
  - Ordnance Department
    - General, 1941-1942 (Folder 20: 14)
      Includes Thirty Division Program correspondence
    - General, 1941-1942 (Folder 21: 1-2)
    - Ammunition, 1941-1942 (Folder 21: 3)
    - Armored division, 1942 (Folder 21: 4)
    - Arsenal correspondence, 1941. (Folder 21: 5)
    - Arsenal inventory, 1941-1943, undated (Folder 21: 6)
    - Arsenal machinery, 1942, undated (Folder 21: 7)
    - Arsenal materials, 1941-1943 (Folder 21: 8-10)
    - Assignments from other countries, 1943 (Folder 22: 1)
    - Assignments vs. requirements, 1943 (Folder 22: 2)
    - British equipment, 1942 (Folder 22: 3)
    - Canadian equipment and supplies, 1941-1942 (Folder 22: 4)
    - Captured ordnance, 1942 (Folder 22: 5)
    - Correspondence, 1941-1942 (Folder 22: 6)
    - Cutting tools, 1941-1942 (Folder 22: 7)
    - Defense Aid Supply Committee, undated (Folder 22: 8)
    - Emergency Air Transport Program, 1942 (Folder 22: 9)
    - Estimated vehicles for infantry, 1943 (Folder 22: 10)
    - Fire control equipment, 1942 (Folder 22: 11)
    - Industrial machinery, 1942-1943 (Folder 22: 12)
    - Lend-Lease Budget, 1942, undated (Folder 22: 13)
    - Material lost at sea, 1942-1943 (Folder 22: 14)
    - Office supplies, 1943-1944 (Folder 22: 15)
    - Releases, 1941-1942 (Folder 22: 16)
    - Requests for assignment of Lend-Lease articles, 1943 (Folder 22: 17)
    - Requirements and assignments (Hsiung's table), undated (Folder 22: 18)
    - Requisitions, status and summaries, 1941, undated (Folder 22: 19)
    - Shipments, 1942 (Folder 22: 20)
    - Shipping schedules and requisitions, 1942, undated (Folder 22: 21-22)
    - Southwest Highway Transport Administration (SWHTA) vehicle reconditioning program, 1944 (Folder 23: 1)
    - Spare parts, 1943 (Folder 23: 2)
    - Status of ordnance program, 1942, undated. (Folder 23: 3)
      Includes Emergency Air Transport Program shipment information
    - Status of requirements after revision of 1943 program (Folder 23: 4)
    - Status reports on assignments and shipments, 1943, undated (Folder 23: 5)
      Includes Thirty Division Program materials
    - Thirty Division Program, 1942, undated (Folder 23: 6)
    - Transfer directive, 1941-1942 (Folder 23: 7)
    - Two pounder guns, 1942 (Folder 23: 8)
    - Worksheets on C-7001, undated (Folder 23: 9)
    - Miscellany, 1941-1942, undated (Folder 23: 10)
  - Signal Corps
    - Air raid warning net, 1941-1943 (Folder 23: 11)
    - Correspondence, 1941-1943, undated (Folder 23: 12-13)
    - Photographic materials, 1942-1943 (Folder 23: 14)
    - Radar, 1942 (Folder 23: 15)
    - Radio equipment for airplanes, 1941-1943 (Folder 23: 16)
    - Requirements, 1944 Lend-Lease Program, signal equipment, Ministry of Communications (Folder 23: 17)
    - Requirements and assignments, 1943-1944 (Folder 23: 18)
    - Resources, 1942 (Folder 23: 19)
    - Shipping (Folder 24)
      - Material to be shipped in two boats, 1942 (Folder 24: 1)
      - Shipments to India for air and land transportation, undated (Folder 24: 2)
    - Signal equipment, 1943 (Folder 24: 3)
    - Stilwell requirements, 1943 (Folder 24: 4)
    - Miscellany, 1941-1944 (Folder 24: 5)
  - Traffic Department
    - General, 1941-1943 (Folder 24: 6-10)
    - Destination of vessels, 1943 (Folder 24: 11)
    - Marking cargo (Folder 24)
      - General, 1942-1944 (Folder 24: 12)
      - Marking sheet, 1941 (Folder 24: 13)
    - Procedures, 1941-1942 (Folder 24: 14)
    - Shipments of Lend-Lease supplies, 1942 (Folder 24: 15)
    - Shipping reports and summaries, 1941-1943 (Folder 24: 16)
    - Shipping requirements, 1942 (Folder 24: 17)
    - Shipping schedules, 1942 (Folder 25: 1)
    - Shipping tickets, 1944 (Folder 25: 2)
    - Summary of Lend-Lease shipments from U.S.A. from May 20, 1941 to June 20, 1942 (Folder 25: 3)
    - Miscellany, 1942-1943 (Folder 25: 4)
- Transportation fuel executive file, 1941-1944 (Box 25-26)
  Includes correspondence, memoranda, reports, and supply lists. Arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - General, 1941-1943 (Folder 25: 5)
  - Aviation gasoline, 1941-1944 (Folder 25: 6)
  - Containers, 1942-1943 (Folder 25: 7)
  - Contracts, 1941-1944 (Folder 25: 8)
  - Conversion of Tung, rapeseed, and other oils, 1942 (Folder 25: 9)
  - Drilling and refining equipment, 1942-1943 (Folder 25: 10)
  - Drum plant, 1942-1943 (Folder 25: 11)
  - Hydrolene, 1942 (Folder 25: 12)
  - Kansu Oil Fields, 1942-1944, undated (Folder 25: 13-15)
  - Natural Resources Commission employees in Far East, 1942-1944 (Folder 25: 16)
  - Petroleum experts, 1942 (Folder 25: 17)
  - Petroleum movements in India and Burma, 1941-1943 (Folder 25: 18)
  - Petroleum requirements, 1941-1942 (Folder 25: 19)
  - Pipeline, 1941-1943. (Folder 26: 1)
    See also Subject file - Burma Road
  - Production, inventory, and consumption in China, 1942-1943 (Folder 26: 2)
  - Requests for allocation, 1941-1943 (Folder 26: 3)
  - Storage tanks and drumming plant, 1943 (Folder 26: 4)
- American Volunteer Group (AVG)/Central Aircraft Manufacturing Company (CAMCO) file, 1941-1947 (Box 26-31)
  Includes financial documents, audits, personnel files, rosters, and correspondence. Arranged alphabetically by subject or format.
  - General, 1941-1945 (Folder 26: 5-10)
    Includes letters from Claire Chennault and T. V. Soong
  - Accounting (Folder 26-27)
    - Accounts and payments (Folder 26-27)
      - General, 1942-1943 (Folder 26: 11)
      - Ahuja, 1946-1947 (Folder 26: 12)
      - Burmah Oil Company, 1942-1945 (Folder 26: 13)
      - Burmah Post and Telegraph, 1944 (Folder 26: 14)
      - China National Aviation Corporation (CNAC), 1944 (Folder 26: 15)
      - Civil Aviation Department, Government of Burman, 1944 (Folder 26: 16)
      - Commissary account, 1942 (Folder 26: 17)
      - General Electric, 1945 (Folder 26: 18)
      - Pinchin, Johnson Co. and Robert Ingham Clark Co., 1941-1944 (Folder 26: 19)
      - Rangoon Office and Plane Assembly Account, 1942 (Folder 26: 20)
      - Roneo, 1944-1945 (Folder 26: 21)
      - Shalimar Paint, Colour & Varnish Co., 1944 (Folder 26: 22)
      - Stand Hotel, Rangoon, and J. W. Darwood, 1944-1945 (Folder 26: 23)
      - Starr, Park and Freeman, 1942-1944 (Folder 27: 1)
      - T. W. Biggs & Biggs, 1942-1944 (Folder 27: 2)
    - Analysis of Major Expense Items, June 2, 1941-February 15,1942 (Folder 27: 3)
    - Audits (Folder 27)
      - Audits for 1941-1942 (Folder 27: 4-7)
      - Correspondence and memoranda, 1942 (Folder 27: 8)
    - Bank of China, 1941-1942 (Folder 27: 9)
    - Debit and credit notes, 1943-1944 (Folder 27: 10)
    - Intercontinent Corporation, 1943-1944 (Folder 27: 11)
    - Memoranda, 1942-1944 (Folder 27: 12)
    - Monthly statements (bank reconciliations), 1941-1942 (Folder 28: 1)
    - Paxton, George L., 1944 (Folder 28: 2)
    - Rangoon advances, 1942 (Folder 28: 3)
    - Receipts and disbursements, 1942-1943 (Folder 28: 4)
    - "Report on the Accounts of Central Aircraft Manufacturing Company Relating to the American Volunteer Group" (Folder 28)
      - Draft, undated (Folder 28: 5)
      - Final report, 1944 (Folder 28: 6)
    - Special Program Fund, 1942-1943 (Folder 28: 7)
  - Action file, 1942-1943 (Folder 28: 8)
  - American Volunteer Group formation, 1941. (Folder 28: 9)
    Includes Curtis-Wright contract
  - American Volunteer Group history and operations, 1942, undated (Folder 28: 10)
  - Bishop, Lewis S., 1941-1943 (Folder 28: 11)
  - Bonus payments, 1942 (Folder 28: 12)
  - Bowers, Thomas S., 1943 (Folder 28: 13)
  - Carney, Boatner R., 1941-1945 (Folder 28: 14)
  - Chennault, Claire, 1941 (Folder 29: 1)
  - Contract, 1942 (Folder 29: 2)
  - Correspondence, 1941-1943 (Folder 29: 3-8)
  - Cuevas, O., 1944-1945 (Folder 29: 9)
  - Employment contract and information, 1941-1944 (Folder 29: 10)
  - Equipment requests, undated (Folder 29: 11)
  - Fatalities, 1942 (Folder 29: 12)
  - Insurance (Folder 29)
    - General, 1942-1943 (Folder 29: 13)
    - Gentry, Thomas C., 1943-1944 (Folder 29: 14)
  - Internal organization, 1941-1942 (Folder 29: 15)
  - Jankski, Edwin A., 1943 (Folder 29: 16)
  - McGarry, William D., 1941-1945 (Folder 29: 17)
  - McGarry, William D., 1941-1945 (Folder 30: 1)
  - Pawley, W.D., 1942 (Folder 30: 2)
  - Office furniture, 1942-1943 (Folder 30: 3)
  - Personnel, General, 1941-1945 (Folder 30: 4-7)
  - Personnel recapitulation, 1941-1942 (Folder 30: 8-9)
  - Personnel reported missing, 1942-1944 (Folder 30: 10)
  - Personnel roster, 1942, undated (Folder 30: 11-12)
  - Personnel, office, 1941-1942 (Folder 31: 1)
  - Pietsker Films, 1942-1943 (Folder 31: 2)
  - Prisoners (AVG personnel taken prisoner), 1943 (Folder 31: 3)
  - Reports to T. V. Soong, 1941-1942 (Folder 31: 4)
  - Requisitions, 1942-1943 (Folder 31: 5)
  - Salary overpayment, 1942-1943 (Folder 31: 6)
  - Tan, W. H., 1944 (Folder 31: 7)
  - Taxes, 1943-1944 (Folder 31: 8)
  - Terry, Julian E., 1942 (Folder 31: 9)
  - Transfer of AVG property to U.S. Army (23rd Pursuit Group), 1942-1943 (Folder 31: 10)
  - Trumble, Thomas G., 1941-1943 (Folder 31: 11)
  - Whelan, Russell, 1942 (Folder 31: 12)
- China National Aviation Corporation (CNAC) file, 1942-1945 (Box 31-32)
  Includes correspondence, price quotations, and supply lists. Arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - General, 1942-1945 (Folder 31: 13-14)
  - Bond, William L. and Bixby, Harold M. cables, 1942-1944 (Folder 31: 15-16)
  - Douglas Airplanes, 1942-1943 (Folder 32: 1)
  - Draft deferments, 1943 (Folder 32: 2)
  - Employment applications, 1943 (Folder 32: 3)
  - Equipment, 1942-1944 (Folder 32: 4)
  - Exchange orders, 1943-1944 (Folder 32: 5)
  - India-China air route, 1942 (Folder 32: 6)
  - Letters of authorization, 1943-1944 (Folder 32: 7)
  - Requisitions, 1942 (Folder 32: 8)
- Speeches and writings, 1940-1945 (Box 32-33)
  Includes typescripts, drafts, correspondence, and printed matter. Arranged alphabetically by author, then by title or format.
  - De Luce, Daniel. "Spurning of Chinese and Lack of Air Force Doomed Burma,", undated (Folder 32: 9)
  - Fly, James Lawrence. "International Communications," talk before the National Lawyers Guild, Washington, D.C., 1943 (Folder 32: 10)
  - Galloway, George B. Postwar Planning in the United States, 1942 (Folder 32: 11)
  - Lattimore, Owen. "How to Win the War,", 1942 (Folder 32: 12)
  - Loening, Grover. "Ships Over the Sea,", 1942 (Folder 32: 13)
  - Maurer. "Situation in China," pre-research draft, 1942 (Folder 32: 14)
  - Maurer. "War in the East,", 1942 (Folder 32: 15)
  - Price, Harry B. "Post War Thinking in the United States,", 1940-1942 (Folder 32: 16)
  - Rajchman, Ludwick. Statements at Onwentsia Conference, 1941. (Folder 33: 1)
    Includes correspondence and biographical note
  - Riesman, David. "Civil Liberties in a Period of Transition,", 1942 (Folder 33: 2)
  - Soong, T.V. (Folder 33)
    - Address at Yale, 1942 (Folder 33: 3)
    - "Address Delivered by Dr. T. V. Soong at Carnegie Hall on October 10, 1942 Under the Auspices of United China Relief," (Folder 33: 4)
    - List of people and agencies to whom Soong's speech was sent, 1942, undated (Folder 33: 5)
    - Research and memoranda, 1942-1944 (Folder 33: 6)
    - Speech, draft, undated (Folder 33: 7)
    - Speech addressed to the president and fellow representatives of the United Nations, circa 1945 (Folder 33: 8)
    - Speech following the address of Soong May-Ling (Madame Chiang Kai-shek), undated (Folder 33: 9)
    - Speech given on the second anniversary of Lend-Lease, draft, 1943 (Folder 33: 10)
  - Stefansson, Vilhjalmur (Folder 33)
    - Arctic Supply Line, 1942 (Folder 33: 11)
    - Correspondence, 1942 (Folder 33: 12)
    - "Depth of the Kolyma River,", 1942 (Folder 33: 13)
    - "Navigation: Seattle to Lena River,", 1942 (Folder 33: 14)
  - Stettinius, Edward R. Lend-Lease manuscript comments, 1942-1943, undated (Folder 33: 15)
  - Tirana, R. "The German Postwar World,", 1940-1941, undated. (Folder 33: 16)
    Includes Ludwik Rajachman article
  - Warner, Edward. "Post-War Transport Aircraft,", 1943 (Folder 33: 17)
- Subject file, 1941-1947 (Box 34-45)
  Includes correspondence, memoranda, and supply lists. Arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - 3-C Program, 1945 (Folder 34: 1)
  - Aircraft Mechanics Training Program, 1943, undated (Folder 34: 2)
  - Air distances, undated (Folder 34: 3)
  - Air freight service, 1941-1942 (Folder 34: 4)
  - Air freight shipments (India to China), 1942 (Folder 34: 5)
  - Air shipments into China, 1943-1944 (Folder 34: 6-7)
  - Air shipping records (Dinjan to Kunming), 1943. (Folder 34: 8)
    Includes CNAC materials
  - Air transport, 1942 (Folder 34: 9)
  - Air transport program (India to China), 1942. (Folder 34: 10)
    See also Emergency Air Transport Program
  - Air transportation materials (Fourth Lend-Lease), 1944 (Folder 34: 11)
  - Air travel regulations, 1944 (Folder 34: 12)
  - Aluminium alloy, 1942 (Folder 34: 13)
  - American loan to China, 1942-1943 (Folder 34: 14)
  - American Technical Mission to India, 1942 (Folder 34: 15)
  - APO numbers, 1944 (Folder 34: 16)
  - Appropriations, 1941-1942 (Folder 34: 17)
  - Appropriations and allocations, 1941 (Folder 34: 18)
  - Bicycle requirements, 1944 (Folder 34: 19)
  - Board of Economic Welfare, 1942 (Folder 34: 20)
  - Board of Transport Control, 1942-1943 (Folder 34: 21)
  - British Supply Council, 1941 (Folder 35: 1)
  - Burma and India, unrest, 1942 (Folder 35: 2)
  - Burma, recapture of, 1942 (Folder 35: 3)
  - Burma Road (Folder 35)
    - General, 1942-1943 (Folder 35: 4)
    - 80,000 ton transportation plan, 1943 (Folder 35: 5)
    - Analysis, 1941-1942 (Folder 35: 6)
    - Arnstein report on trucking, 1941 (Folder 35: 7)
    - Chen, R.C., correspondence on Leland Stowe's book They Shall Not Sleep, 1944 (Folder 35: 8)
    - Customs duties, 1941 (Folder 35: 9)
    - Pipeline, 1941-1943. (Folder 35: 10)
      See also Transportation fuel executive file
    - "Plans for the Rehabilitation of Overland Transportation in Burma,", 1942-1943 (Folder 35: 11)
    - Rehabilitation, 1942 (Folder 35: 12)
    - Stationary repair shops, 1941, undated (Folder 35: 13)
    - Transportation facilities, 1941 (Folder 35: 14)
  - Burma-Yunnan Railway, 1941-1942 (Folder 35: 15)
  - Canada, 1941-1943 (Folder 35: 16)
  - Cement plants, 1943 (Folder 35: 17)
  - hapter numbers, aviation markings and contracts, undated (Folder 35: 18)
  - China (Folder 35)
    - General, 1942-1943, undated (Folder 35: 19)
    - Airline proposals (from Consolidated Vultee Aircraft Corporation), 1945 (Folder 35: 20)
    - Three Year Plan for Wartime Reconstruction, 1941 (Folder 35: 21)
  - China Supply Program memoranda, 1943 (Folder 35: 22)
  - Chinese air cadets, 1943 (Folder 35: 23)
  - Chinese Arsenal Supply Program, 1942-1944 (Folder 35: 24)
  - Chinese Exclusion Act, 1942-1943 (Folder 36: 1)
  - Chinese Exclusion Act, repeal, 1942-1943 (Folder 36: 2)
  - Chinese Port Program, 1946 (Folder 36: 3)
  - Chinese requirements and memoranda for Louis Johnson, 1942 (Folder 36: 4)
  - Chinese requirements that are transportable by air (Shaughnessy memorandum), 1943 (Folder 36: 5)
  - Chinese Military Mission, 1942-1943 (Folder 36: 6)
  - Clippings, 1943-1944, undated (Folder 36: 7)
  - Committee on Motion Picture Projects, 1945 (Folder 36: 8)
  - Committee on Training Projects, 1943-1944 (Folder 36: 9)
  - Committee to Defend America by Aiding the Allies, 1941 (Folder 36: 10)
  - Communism, 1941-1942. (Folder 36: 11)
    Includes typescripts
  - Community War Fund, 1943 (Folder 36: 12)
  - Consignment of Lend-Lease goods procedure, 1942 (Folder 36: 13)
  - Contemporary China newsletter (Chinese Industrial Development), 1943 (Folder 36: 14)
  - Defense articles, release and cancellations, 1941 (Folder 36: 15)
  - Dictaphone radio recording equipment, 1943 (Folder 36: 16)
  - Diversion of Supplies, 1942-1944 (Folder 36: 17-18)
  - Electrolytic nickel, 1941 (Folder 36: 19)
  - Emergency Air Transport Program. (Folder 36-37)
    See also Minimum Chinese Program and Air Transport Program
    - First program, 1942 (Folder 36: 20)
    - Second program, 1942 (Folder 36: 21)
    - Second program, requests for assignments, 1942 (Folder 37: 1)
  - Employment of Chinese seaman (agreement between British and Chinese governments), 1942-1943 (Folder 37: 2)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1942 (Folder 37: 3)
  - Film cartridges, 1942-1944 (Folder 37: 4)
  - Foreign Economic Administration (FEA), 1944 (Folder 37: 5)
  - Foreign post exchange purchasing, 1942 (Folder 37: 6)
  - General Motors (Folder 37)
    - Overseas operations, undated (Folder 37: 7)
    - Rangoon assembly plant, 1941-1942 (Folder 37: 8)
  - Haas Mission (malaria), 1941-1942 (Folder 37: 9)
  - Higgins Industries, 1943. (Folder 37: 10)
    Includes Bernhard report
  - Highway distances, undated (Folder 37: 11)
  - India (Folder 37-38)
    - General, 1942-1943 (Folder 37: 12)
    - Chinese organization in India, 1943 (Folder 37: 13)
    - "Communications Between India and China," report on suggested route from Bengal to China, undated. (Folder 37: 14)
      Includes photographs. See also Oversize Materials for maps
    - Diversions, 1943 (Folder 37: 15)
    - India-China railway, 1943 (Folder 37: 16)
    - Indian government (appointment of Zajrullah Khan), 1942 (Folder 37: 17)
    - Indian mission, 1942 (Folder 37: 18)
    - Indian stockpile of China materials, 1943 (Folder 37: 19)
    - Material en Route and in India as of April 1, 1943 (Folder 37-38)
      - Original. Copy in Box:38 (Folder 37: 20)
      - Use copy (Folder 38: 1)
    - Supplies, 1943 (Folder 38: 2)
    - Supplies to Chinese groups in India at Base X-Ray and Ramgarh, 1943 (Folder 38: 3-5)
    - Supplies to Chinese troops, 1944 (Folder 38: 6)
    - Transportation, land and sea routes, 1941-1943 (Folder 38: 7)
  - Intelligence report on Japanese aviation, proposed changes, 1943 (Folder 38: 8)
  - Iranian route (Folder 38-39)
    - Correspondence, letters, 1942-1943 (Folder 38: 9)
    - Correspondence, telegrams, 1943 (Folder 38: 10)
    - India-Iran-Russia supply route, 1942-1943 (Folder 38: 11)
    - Reports and progress memoranda, 1942-1943 (Folder 39: 1)
    - Requests for assignment, 1942-1943 (Folder 39: 2)
    - Shipments from U.S., 1943 (Folder 39: 3)
    - Trucks, 1942-1943 (Folder 39: 4-5)
    - Trucks for Chinese end of route, 1942-1944 (Folder 39: 6)
    - Tweedy and Chow report on Trans-Iranian Highway, 1943 (Folder 39: 7-8)
  - International Division (Folder 39)
    - Missions Branch, 1942 (Folder 39: 9)
    - Organization, 1942-1943 (Folder 39: 10)
    - Procedures for requisitions, 1943 (Folder 39: 11)
    - Services of Supply organization chart, undated (Folder 39: 12)
  - International Supply Committee, directory, 1942 (Folder 39: 13)
  - Japanese Broadcasts, undated. (Folder 40: 1)
    Originally labelled "Propaganda"
  - Land supply routes to China, 1942-1943 (Folder 40: 2)
  - Legislation, 1941-1943 (Folder 40: 3)
  - Lend-Lease (Folder 40)
    - Agreement, 1946-1947 (Folder 40: 4)
    - Budget (Folder 40)
      - First, second and third Lend-Lease, 1941-1942 (Folder 40: 5)
      - Fourth Lend-Lease, 1942-1943 (Folder 40: 6)
      - Fifth Lend-Lease, 1944 (Folder 40: 7)
      - Sixth Lend-Lease, 1946 (Folder 40: 8)
    - China, 1942, undated (Folder 40: 9)
    - House Bill and agreement with China, 1941-1942 (Folder 40: 10)
    - Preliminary summary of value of shipments, 1944 (Folder 40: 11)
    - Procedures, 1942 (Folder 40: 12)
    - Requisitions filed, 1941-1944 (Folder 40: 13-15)
    - Requisitions (lists and status reports), 1942 (Folder 41: 1)
    - Status report, 1943 (Folder 41: 2)
  - Machine tools, 1942 (Folder 41: 3)
  - Mechanics Training Program, 1943 (Folder 41: 4)
  - Metals, 1941 (Folder 41: 5)
  - Minimum Chinese Program, 1942 (Folder 41: 6)
  - Munitions Assignments Board, 1942 (Folder 41: 7)
  - National resources, 1941-1944 (Folder 41: 8)
  - Natural Resources Commission and MS Day Star, 1943 (Folder 41: 9)
  - Nitrates, 1942 (Folder 41: 10)
  - Office of War Information, 1942 (Folder 41: 11)
  - Oil companies, undated (Folder 41: 12)
  - Oil situation in China, 1943 (Folder 41: 13)
  - Pacific War Council, 1942 (Folder 41: 14)
  - Plan to expedite shipping and transportation from Rangoon to Kunming by T. B. Wilson, undated (Folder 41: 15)
  - Polish Air Force, 1942 (Folder 41: 16)
  - Port Program, 1945, undated (Folder 41: 17)
  - Post war planning, 1943, undated (Folder 41: 18)
  - Power plants, 1941-1946 (Folder 41: 19-21)
  - Preference rating applications correspondence, 1942 (Folder 41: 22)
  - Preference rating (PD-1 A) forms, 1942 (Folder 41: 23)
  - President [draft of letter, possibly to Franklin Roosevelt], undated (Folder 41: 24)
  - Priorities, 1942 (Folder 41: 25)
  - Procedure for defense aid, 1942 (Folder 41: 26)
  - Procedure governing transfer of custody of Chinese government stores to U.S. Army, 1942 (Folder 42: 1)
  - Proposed pipeline across Florida, undated (Folder 42: 2)
  - Punch and die steel, 1942 (Folder 42: 3)
  - Radio, telephone and telegraph, 1941-1942 (Folder 42: 4)
  - Railway and highway requirements (Third Lend-Lease), 1942 (Folder 42: 5)
  - Reports (Folder 42)
    - Bernhard report (Higgins Industries), 1943-1944 (Folder 42: 6)
    - "Engineering Report on Substitute Fuels" by Alex Taub et al., 1945 (Folder 42: 7)
    - "Harbor Projects,", undated (Folder 42: 8)
    - "Preliminary Development of Porcelain Insulators and Appliances Manufacturing Corporation,", undated (Folder 42: 9)
    - "Preliminary Development of the Central Radio Corporation,", undated (Folder 42: 10)
    - "Preliminary Development of Wire Tele-Communications Equipment Manufacturing Plant,", undated (Folder 42: 11)
    - Purchase Negotiation Reports (Folder 42)